A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
- Records - Accession 50624, 1865-1988., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 47-60)
  - Lot 12962 - Papers of Lorraine Graves and Michael Webster,1971-1983. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Lot 12977 - Papers of Dorothy Crandall,1981. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Lot 12978 - Papers of Jerome and Elmora Crews,1972. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Lot 12979 - Papers of Lawana Cross,1924-1980. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Lot 12981 - Papers of Artiemese Cruthird,1977-1978. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Lot 12986 - Papers of Alonzo DeBerry,1970-1989. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Lot 12988 - Papers of Michael Dills and Anne Evans,1962-1963. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Lot 12990 - Papers of P. M. Eddleton,1941-1950. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Lot 12992 - Papers of Eloise F. Broadnax,1980. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Lot 12994 - Papers of Leslie Phillips,1943-1971. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Lot 12999 - Papers of Gertrude M. Farmer,1978. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Lot 13000 - Papers of Raymond Gariel,1954-1974. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Lot 13008 - Papers of William Goldman, Jr.,1967. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Lot 13010 - Papers of the Goode and Capps Families,1905-1952. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Lot 13016 - Papers of Constance Jennifer Muncy,1985. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Lot 13017 - Papers of John D. Gribbin,1981. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Lot 13019 - Papers of Carl B. Hairston,1979-1983. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Lot 13022 - Papers of Anne Briscoe,1983. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Lot 13024 - Papers of Charles Harper,1966-1970. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Lot 13037 - Papers of John and Karen Holley,1981. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Lot 13038 - Papers of Clark Hopkins and Alice Jackson,1917-1971. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Lot 13044 - Papers of Charles and Jean Hudson,1959-1977. (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Lot 13046 - Papers of Dorothy Hughes,1962. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Lot 13047 - Papers of Bill Hunt,1960-1979. (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Lot 13052 - Papers of Justine Johnson,1956. (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Lot 13055 - Papers of Pearl Rustin and George L. Jones,1974-1976. (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Lot 13058 - Papers of Anthony and Anne Kachergis,1925-1965. (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Lot 13061 - Papers of Gloria Kuldell,1942-1975. (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Lot 13062 - Papers of Walter L. Keller,1919-1948. (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Lot 13063 - Papers of William R. King,1973-1980. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Lot 13067 - Papers of Steven Cavanaugh Manning,1949-1980. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Lot 13068 - Papers of Russell and Millicent Lawrence,1973. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Lot 13070 - Papers of Theon Lee,1970-1981. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Lot 13072 - Papers of James and Suzanne Lehner,1973. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Lot 13073 - Papers of Luisita Lemaster,1958-1985. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Lot 13075 - Papers of Romanuel and Naomi Lewis,1975. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Lot 13077 - Papers of George Lewis,1910-1973. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Lot 13079 - Papers of George R. Lundy,1925-1973. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Lot 13081 - Papers of Iren Marik,1905-1963. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Lot 13087 - Papers of Gary and Dianne McNaught,1966-1974. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Lot 13098 - Papers of Robert Maggard,1965-1968. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Lot 13100 - Papers of Alice and Marion Meredith,1928-1967. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Lot 13102 - Papers of George D. Mills,1949-1981. (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Lot 13109 - Papers of Barbara Jean Porter,1985. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Lot 13121 - Papers of Ira Oursler,1915-1920. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Lot 13126 - Papers of Raymond and Linda Payne,1974-1978. (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Lot 13130 - Papers of John and Virginia Harten Phillips,1908-1972. (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Lot 13131 - Papers of Alice Bonham Grubb,1938-1956. (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Lot 13134 - Papers of Sarah J. El,1901-1976. (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Lot 13138 - Papers of Virginia O. Armstrong,1922-1962. (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Lot 13139 - Papers of Robert and Florence Reynolds,1893-1973. (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Lot 13148 - Papers of Denise Van Chieri and John J. Ryan,1946-1980. (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Lot 13151 - Papers of Raymond and Mary Salmon,1959-1972. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Lot 13162 - Papers of Tina Gore Smith,1985. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Lot 13178 - Papers of Mary Thomas and Judge James Lee,1968-1978. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Lot 13295 - Papers of John and Linda Wiggins,1979. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Lot 13298 - Papers of Rosalie Davidson Atkinson,1963-1981. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Lot 13304 - Papers of Alex Crawley and Sylvia W. Scott,1910-1974. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Lot 13311 - Papers of Garnett Gregory,1973-1981. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Lot 13312 - Papers of Lillian Nace,1980. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Lot 13323 - Papers of Jeremiah Morgan,1959-1974. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Lot 13328 - Papers of Ruth K. Hardin Brewer,1981. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Lot 13334 - Papers of Ralph M. Thompson,1973-1980. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Lot 13340 - Papers of Richard and Maria Otto,1962-1981. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Lot 13341 - Papers of Robert Gollahon,1977-1980. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Lot 13344 - Papers of Barbara Parkin,1947-1980. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Lot 13350 - Papers of Stephen W. Puschman,1938. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Lot 13351 - Papers of Betty J. Howell,1975-1976. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Lot 13357 - Papers of Norman F. DiBucci,1931-1976. (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Lot 13359 - Papers of Vivian Platsky Davit Michel,1967-1982. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Lot 13378 - Papers of David and Maria Greenburg,1968. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Lot 13380 - Papers of Elizabeth Lecompte and Dale Shenk,1974. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Lot 13383 - Papers of Lydia O. Grimberg,1889-1968. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Lot 13385 - Papers of Charles B. and Carolyn Bruce MacLean,1943-1971. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Lot 13395 - Papers of Peggy Martin,1971-1981. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Lot 13399 - Papers of Frank J. Kelly,1940-1982. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Lot 13404 - Papers of William Graff,1945-1985. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Lot 13409 - Papers of Thomas and Jean COhn,1974-1979. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Lot 13413 - Papers of Evelyn J. Bowman,1975-1980. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Lot 13421 - Papers of Beverly S. Johnson,1975-1980. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lot 13422 - Papers of David and Loretta Greenfield,1966-1975. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Lot 13425 - Papers of Rhonda Hamlet Van Lowe,1952-1981. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Lot 13431 - Papers of Curtis and Maartje Rosenberg,1980. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Lot 13433 - Papers of Robert Dean Griffin,1946. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Lot 13437 - Papers of Thomas F. Coyne, Jr.,1932-1966. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Lot 13443 - Papers of Albert and Carol Cunningham,1980. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lot 13447 - Papers of Brian and Nancy Keaveny,1966-1976. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Lot 13448 - Papers of Charles D. Haines,1977-1981. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Lot 13461 - Papers of Richard Lamor Parler,1907. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Lot 13469 - Papers of Samuel and Marcia Becker,1961-1967. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Lot 13470 - Papers of Jerry and Beverly McPeeks,1980-1985. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Lot 13472 - Papers of Walter Lee Taylor,1935-1981. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Lot 13484 - Papers of Jean Opal Campbell,1943-1980. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Lot 157932 - Papers of Richard K. Wood,1927-1974. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Lot 1394498 - Papers of Willis and Jacqueline Kearney,1970. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of Margaret L. Boyd,1917-1972. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of Marilyn S. Hodges,1947-1986. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Unnumbered lot - Papers of James J. and Paula E. Kenney,1944-1976. (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Records - Accession 52072, 1862-1988., Extent: 17 boxes. (Box 61-77)
  By lot number.
  - Lot 3333 - Papers of Frank Tignor,1966-1973. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Lot 3356 - Papers of Mary and Herbert Cushing, 1941-1971. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Lot 3360 - Papers of Pamela Bangley or Jack Holland, 1975. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Lot 3523 - Papers of Dewey D. Spangler, 1963. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Lot 3538 - Papers of Kyle H. Lynch, 1967. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Lot 3646 - Papers of James Russell Craig, 1955. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Lot 4533 - Papers of Jethero Tillman, 1940-1985. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5244 - Papers of Edward F. Curtin III, 1967-1975. (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5244 - Papers of Edward F. Curtin III, 1975, n.d. (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5246 - Papers of Earl Lee Barnes, 1974. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5252 - Papers of Marvin and Phyllis Crane, 1958. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5253 - Papers of Jean J. DeRener, 1957-1971. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5256 - Papers of David and Rebecca Alderson,. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5257 - Papers of Lorie Buterbaugh, 1977. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5259 - Papers of Russell and Barbara Herrick, 1957-1966. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5261 - Papers of Donald Mitchell, 1972. (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5263 - Papers of Margaret R. Hughes, 1919-1946. (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5266 - Papers of James B. Bates, 1974. (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5267 - Papers of Horace and Valerie Brittain, 1974. (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5268 - Papers of William Coffey and Linda Casper, 1948-1974. (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5270 - Papers of Ritchie and Jane Jones, 1971-1973. (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5271 - Papers of Billy R. King, 1969. (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Lot 5272 - Papers of Carol G. and Wesse C. Ranes III, 1945-1972. (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Lot 5274 - Papers of Darlene Trumbo, 1950. (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Lot 5276 - Papers of Joanne E. Thomas, 1975. (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Lot 5278 - Papers of Charlene and Raymond Marlowe, 1977-1978. (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Lot 5280 - Papers of Gwendolyn and D. Paul Batchellor, 1972-1973. (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Lot 5284 - Papers of Maurice E. Bennett, Jr., n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5286 - Papers of Dennis A. Collette, 1978. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5287 - Papers of Michael and Mildred Saunders, 1979. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5289 - Papers of Larry L. Clerk, 1976. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5290 - Papers of Donald Raye Guthrie, 1972-1974. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5293 - Papers of Louis Maxey, 1970-1978. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5295 - Papers of Boyd Tankersley, 1972-1974. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5306 - Papers of Wayne and June Heideman, 1975. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5308 - Papers of Victor D. Chambers, 1965-1971. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5309 - Papers of Jamie N. Leiberg, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5310 - Papers of Eric E. Johnson, 1981. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5313 - Papers of Ricky and Shirley Odle, 1957-1978. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5314 - Papers of Lee and Barbara Perry, 1977-1980. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5316 - Papers of Mary Ann Abrams, 1972. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5317 - Papers of Charlie D. Adkins, 1935-1971. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5318 - Papers of Edward Baker, 1947-1959. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5320 - Papers of Bennie and Verline Baskerville, 1979. (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5322 - Papers of Paul Bentley, 1976. (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5324 - Papers of Bruce and Charlotte Burkett, 1973-1978. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5327 - Papers of Clyde and Beulah Carter, 1933-1973. (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5330 - Papers of James and Barbara Combs, 1967-1972. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5332 - Papers of Fred and Dyanne McCutchon, 1959-1981. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Lot 5336 - Papers of David and Robin Porter, 1974. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Lot 5341 - Papers of Carl E. Thompson, 1967. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Lot 5342 - Papers of Papers of Carole P. Daly or Susan P. Stone, 1977-1979. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5344 - Papers of Carlyle and Diane Deane, 1969-1977. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5346 - Papers of Charles A. Diggs, 1969-1977. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5347 - Papers of Walter and Phyllis Dodge, 1974-1977. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5349 - Papers of Douglas M. Felts and Robert Ward, 1978-1979. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5351 - Papers of W. H. Fletcher, 1926-1947. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5352 - Papers of Lonnie Fulford, Jr., 1978. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5359 - Papers of Marcul L. Gunnells, 1953. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5360 - Papers of Miriam Haggar, 1966-1967. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5362 - Papers of Jerry Hale, 1975-1978. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5363 - Papers of Jim D. Wayne Hammonds, 1973. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5370 - Papers of Laurence Hargrave, 1977. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5370 - Papers of M. M. Harris, 1974. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5371 - Papers of Henry and Victoria Hidalgo, 1947-1975. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5377 - Papers of JoAnn Johnsey, 1978. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5377 - Papers of Johnny and Gloria Johnson, 1951-1977. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5379 - Papers of Annie Kelly, 1979. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5380 - Papers of Michael and Christine Kerwin, 1947-1973. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5381 - Papers of Carol J. Kessler, 1974. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5385 - Papers of Shirley R. Kosma, 1961-1976. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5386 - Papers of Craig R. Logan, 1971-1979. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5390 - Papers of Thelma McFarland, 1980. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Lot 5391 - Papers of Barbara McMurray, 1971. (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Lot 5392 - Papers of Kenneth W. Miller, 1965-1976. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Lot 5393 - Papers of Henry and Elizabeth Mitts, 1977-1978. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Lot 5394 - Papers of Helen E. Mombaerts, 1934-1976. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Lot 5396 - Papers of Michael D. Morris, 1977. (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Lot 5397 - Papers of Nadina Musick, 1897-1979. (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Lot 5399 - Papers of Old Virginia, Inc., 1910-1973. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5400 - Papers of Priscilla Easter Owens, 1980-1981. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5402 - Papers of Joyce M. Pettaway, 1948-1977. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5405 - Papers of Patricia and Leonard Provost, 1946-1976. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5408 - Papers of Carl and Effie Reed, 1969. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5409 - Papers of Martha B. Riddick, 1892-1973. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5410 - Papers of Geraldine G. Riley, 1939. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5412 - Papers of Edward and Victoria Rose, 1974. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5413 - Papers of Luala M. Ruiz, 1969-1973. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5418 - Papers of Ann B. Sulkie, 1969. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5419 - Papers of Burma R. Sykes, 1973. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5421 - Papers of the Vocational Education Foundation, 1977-1980. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5422 - Papers of Ollie Ward, 1924-1979. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5423 - Papers of Cynthia and Robert Wayland III, 1966-1969. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5427 - Papers of the World Asset Exchange, Inc., 1981. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5428 - Papers of Rosalie R. Carroll, 1955-1966. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5431 - Papers of J. Kennedy Sills, 1956. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5432 - Papers of Marvin L. Friedman, 1966-1968. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5433 - Papers of John Day, Jr., 1971. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5435 - Papers of Charles and Chong Cha Surratt, 1967-1976. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5436 - Papers of Marjorie R. Barnes, 1942-1972. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5438 - Papers of Larry A. Leisner, 1979. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5440 - Papers of Viola M. Jones, 1967-1976. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5443 - Papers of Jack Randall Pugh, 1966. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5445 - Papers of Ronnie H. Spencer, 1980. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5446 - Papers of Paul and Barbara Jureidini, 1935-1962. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5447 - Papers of John M. Schmelzer, 1975-Sep. 1980. (1 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5447 - Papers of John M. Schmelzer, Dec. 1980-1982. (2 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5447 - Papers of John M. Schmelzer, n.d. (3 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5449 - Papers of Charles L. Harlan, 1920-1962. (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5450 - Papers of Cycle Systems Index, Inc., 1951. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5453 - Papers of James and Mary Ann Irvin, 1966. (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5456 - Papers of James and Margaret Waters, 1951-1964. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5457 - Papers of Marie Haynes, 1971-1972. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5459 - Papers of Lynn Peterson and Stephen Snyder, 1973. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5460 - Papers of Vernon L. Marshall, 1941-1979. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5463 - Papers of Irving W. Martin, 1944. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5464 - Papers of Charles Wynne, 1940-1977. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5465 - Papers of Gerald and Joan Faist, 1944-1977. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5469 - Papers of Robert R. Foley, 1979. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5471 - Papers of Thomas and Anna Lackey, 1930-1978. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5473 - Papers of Leon and Cynthia Hundley, 1977. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5478 - Papers of Judy H. Kluis, 1982. (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5479 - Papers of William J. Landen, 1862-1941. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5480 - Papers of Robert and Edith Ziegler, 1950-1967. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5481 - Papers of Philip Sevold and Ida Buchanan, 1947-1949. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5482 - Papers of Joseph and Shirley Ann Faye, 1948. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5483 - Papers of Larry Martin, 1959. (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5484 - Papers of H. H. Whitfield, 1942-1954. (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5491 - Papers of Rev. Richard W. Green, 1969. (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5492 - Papers of Ernest and Edith Fender, 1902-1942. (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5493 - Papers of Ollie R. Chaney, 1926-1934. (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5497 - Papers of Barbara Bracken, 1944-1973. (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5499 - Papers of Joseph C. Cogliano, 1971-1972. (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Lot 5500 - Papers of Peggy Pitcock and Delmar Linden Dehaven, Jr., 1967-1970. (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Lot 5501 - Papers of Louise V. Hedrick, 1965-1975. (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Lot 5502 - Papers of Adrienna Honesty, 1976-1978. (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Lot 5503 - Papers of Alan and Judith Reid, 1975. (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Lot 5507 - Papers of Emilio Bacarezza, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5510 - Papers of Karen and Lawrence Downing, 1952-1979. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5511 - Papers of George and Mary Barnes, 1932-1973. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5513 - Papers of Edward James Bill, 1957-1982. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5516 - Papers of Kathy and John Bridgins, 1952-1978. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5527 - Papers of Loretta R. Deboissiere, 1961-1962. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5529 - Papers of Henry R. Doyle, 1958-1963. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5531 - Papers of Wayne and Alice Dunn, 1907-1969. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5536 - Papers of Helena R. Evans, 1945-1982. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5537 - Papers of Nicholas and George E. Georges, 1982. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5538 - Papers of Gertrude and John Gibson, Jr., 1902-1973. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5539 - Papers of William L. Bonaparte, 1981. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5540 - Papers of Gerard and Pamela Hart, 1977-1978. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5543 - Papers of Sylvia and Michael Heilman,. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5547 - Papers of Kevin and Carolyn Hoare, 1962-1983. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5550 - Papers of Margaret Jenkins, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5551 - Papers of Joan B. Jones, 1980-1982. (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5552 - Papers of Burnic and Mary Keyes, 1934-1979. (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5554 - Papers of Robert and Susan Killion, 1979. (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5557 - Papers of Edward Law, 1942-1975. (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5560 - Papers of Robert M. Mears, 1977-1979. (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5562 - Papers of Henry Miller, 1975-1982. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5563 - Papers of Lee Martin O'Brien, 1902-1980. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5565 - Papers of Robert G. Owen, 1984. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5566 - Papers of James and Annmarie Raynor, 1984. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5567 - Papers of Dr. Lord Cecil Rhodes, 1964-1971. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5569 - Papers of Clara Richardson, 1984-1985. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5570 - Papers of Bennie Rivers, 1981. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5573 - Papers of Rev. Verley L. Smith, 1956-1984. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5575 - Papers of Howard and Hazel Smoot, 1921-1969. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5578 - Papers of Charlene Strickland, 1941-1984. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5580 - Papers of Sonja and Terry Waters, 1949-1982. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5583 - Papers of Leslie J. Zell, 1948-1983. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5585 - Papers of Khalid Al-Thumaini, 1980-1981. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5587 - Papers of Nellie W. Walton, 1944-1973. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5593 - Papers of Vickey S. Bryant, 1979. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5594 - Papers of Elwood S. Burton, 1971. (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5596 - Papers of Sally Craver, 1970-1974. (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5598 - Papers of Raymond S. Harris, 1979. (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5603 - Papers of Daniel Arley Scott, 1969-1977. (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5700 - Papers of Carlton Hoggard, 1986. (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Lot 5710 - Papers of Bart E. Williams, 1964-1983. (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Lot 5876 - Papers of Richard Rizer, 1950. (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Lot 5894 - Papers of Bettieanne B. Parmer, 1944-1981. (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Lot 5895 - Papers of Irene Pound, 1962-1983. (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Lot 5915 - Papers of Edward F. Stillinger, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Lot 5922 - Papers of James Michael Allred, 1969-1978. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5928 - Papers of Linda Starr Davis, 1980. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Lot 5929 - Papers of Dr. Colonious Davis and Maude Thigpen, 1943-1948. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Lot 5930 - Papers of Patricia Davis, 1966-1976. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Lot 5932 - Papers of Paul J. Ensminger III, 1977-1978. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Lot 5937 - Papers of Earl Gibbs and William E. Fisher, 1943-1969. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Lot 5943 - Papers of Carol V. Gordan, 1970-1975. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Lot 5945 - Papers of Ronald P. Hammers, 1974-1977. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Lot 5947 - Papers of William and Mary Hilburn, 1973. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Lot 5949 - Papers of Ronald and Loretta James, 1969-1977. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Lot 5950 - Papers of Mary Kaiser, 1977-1979. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Lot 5953 - Papers of Elizabeth H. (Knight) Killen, 1970-1976. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Lot 5954 - Papers of Elizabeth and Alton Malpass, 1943-1956. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Lot 5955 - Papers of Evertt Meixel, 1977. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Lot 5957 - Papers of Henry Overstreet, 1976. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Lot 5960 - Papers of Pat Powell, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Lot 5961 - Papers of John and Katherine McLeod, 1971-1973. (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Lot 5963 - Papers of Vassie and Barnett E. Reeves, Jr., 1972-1973. (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Lot 5968 - Papers of Clara Wilson Short,. (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Lot 5969 - Papers of Cecil J. Waters, 1953-1964. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Lot 5970 - Papers of Albert Williams, 1979-1980. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6020 - Papers of Anna L. Williams, 1979. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6023 - Papers of Calvin Lee White, 1988. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6026 - Papers of James Cotton, 1987-1988. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6029 - Papers of Raymond Wheeler, 1983-1987. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6032 - Papers of William Snead, Jr., 1964-1978. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6041 - Papers of Cleveland N. Cary, 1985-1988. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6042 - Papers of Curtis F. Salsbury, 1987. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6047 - Papers of Mary D. Kaloostian, 1907. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6055 - Papers of Kathleen Gray, 1984. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6130 - Papers of Renita Clark, 1975. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6131 - Papers of Francis E. Dale, 1970. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6133- Papers of Paul Adams, Jr., 1975-1977. (Box 70, Folder 14)